{
    "subject": "resource/Antony_Sher",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Naturalised_citizens_of_the_United_Kingdom",
    "human_readable": "Antony Sher's subject category is Naturalised citizens of the United Kingdom.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6215620040893555,
            "question": "What are the requirements for becoming a naturalized citizen of the UK?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6126895546913147,
            "question": "Can you name other famous naturalized citizens of the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6023024916648865,
            "question": "Was Antony Sher born in the United Kingdom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46328476071357727,
            "question": "What does it mean to be a 'naturalised citizen'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4470522403717041,
            "question": "To which country did Antony Sher gain citizenship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31324318051338196,
            "question": "What are some benefits of becoming a naturalized citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2947966158390045,
            "question": "Why do people choose to become naturalized citizens of other countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2882300615310669,
            "question": "How does someone's cultural background influence their experience as a naturalized citizen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27655288577079773,
            "question": "What challenges might a naturalized citizen face in their new country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2713484764099121,
            "question": "What nationality was Antony Sher?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Antony Sher's subject category is Naturalised citizens of the United Kingdom.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5892_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What challenges might a naturalized citizen face in their new country?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5892_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does someone's cultural background influence their experience as a naturalized citizen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5892_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why do people choose to become naturalized citizens of other countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5892_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_152.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5892_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Antony Sher becoming a British citizen in 1979, which supports his classification as a naturalized citizen of the United Kingdom. Therefore, the statement \"Antony Sher's subject category is Naturalised citizens of the United Kingdom\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context, there are multiple pieces of information that support the notion that Antony Sher was a naturalized citizen of the United Kingdom. Specifically, it mentions that \"Sher became a British citizen in 1979.\" Therefore, the statement aligns with the document's content.\n\nHere is the structured JSON format response:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Antony Sher became a British citizen in 1979, not before that.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Antony Sher became a British citizen in 1979, which implies he was not born as a naturalized citizen of the United Kingdom.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}